<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abs on EN</title>
    <link>https://edu-transformer.github.io/abs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abs on EN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://edu-transformer.github.io/abs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT in School: How to Start?</title>
      <link>https://edu-transformer.github.io/abs/2310.0101/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edu-transformer.github.io/abs/2310.0101/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT in School: How to Start? Author: Collective work SLO5, Publication: Oct 26 2023, License: CC BYChatGPT has sparked a debate on how modern education should adapt to the rapidly changing reality.
Participants of the debate at SLO5 high school concluded: The topic of Artificial Intelligence (AI) needs to be introduced into the curriculum. The nature of homework should change, and awareness should be raised. AI will not replace full engagement in learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech&#39;s Rapid Growth: A Challenge for Humanity</title>
      <link>https://edu-transformer.github.io/abs/2310.0001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edu-transformer.github.io/abs/2310.0001/</guid>
      <description>Tech&amp;rsquo;s Rapid Growth: A Challenge for Humanity Source: Nobel Prize YouTube Channel, Abstract: GTP-4, Publication: 26 Paź 2023Tristan Harris discusses the rapid growth of technology, especially artificial intelligence (AI) and social media&amp;rsquo;s impact. Highlighting a challenge, he cites EO Wilson, a renowned sociobiologist, who said:
&amp;ldquo;The real problem of humanity is that we have Paleolithic emotions, medieval institutions, and god-like Technology.&amp;rdquo;
This quote underscores the gap between our basic emotions, old institutions, and powerful modern tech.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
