<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Edu Transformer on EN</title>
    <link>https://edu-transformer.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Edu Transformer on EN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://edu-transformer.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://edu-transformer.github.io/platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edu-transformer.github.io/platform/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re building a publishing platform. Think academic journals, but way simpler.
Your Piece: Go solo or team up. Share your work and let others build upon it.
How to Draft?: Describe a problem, showcase your results, then hint at possible uses. As for length? You decide.
For Instance: How about leveraging ChatGPT to make a tough topic engaging?
After Submission: No grades here! Just checking for fit with our project goals and general standards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Involved</title>
      <link>https://edu-transformer.github.io/get-involved/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edu-transformer.github.io/get-involved/</guid>
      <description>How It Works: You can work alone or in a team. We&amp;rsquo;re piloting at SLO5 high school, but we&amp;rsquo;re open to more schools and people. Interested? Contact us.
Our Team sets themes and reviews submissions. Schools joining us need a lead to review local submissions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hallucination and Bias Hunter: Understand Human and Technological Limitations</title>
      <link>https://edu-transformer.github.io/hunter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edu-transformer.github.io/hunter/</guid>
      <description>Hallucination and Bias Hunter We live in a world where reality and technology influence each other in ways that can be hard to comprehend. It&amp;rsquo;s worth asking a few questions: Which would leave a bigger digital footprint, a peaceful demonstration or one that turns violent? An outrageous statement or a balanced one?
Understanding the limitations and weaknesses of our brain is crucial, but it&amp;rsquo;s equally important to grasp the constraints of technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lesson Transformer: Technology supports educational transformation</title>
      <link>https://edu-transformer.github.io/transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edu-transformer.github.io/transformer/</guid>
      <description>Lesson Transformer Have you ever felt trapped in an endless scroll on social media, while on the other hand, finding the school curriculum hardly engaging? Social media employs captivating strategies to hold our attention. Could we leverage such engaging power for educational purposes? Let&amp;rsquo;s explore ways to transform traditionally perceived boring subjects into captivating lessons with the help of artificial intelligence. Here are some ways you can utilize language models (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness Master: Technology supports mindfulness</title>
      <link>https://edu-transformer.github.io/master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edu-transformer.github.io/master/</guid>
      <description>Mindfulness Master Mindfulness is crucial for the learning process. However, in the digital world, &amp;lsquo;Attention Thieves&amp;rsquo; are ubiquitous. Let&amp;rsquo;s consider how we can use technology to support us in becoming more mindful, focused, and aware. Here are some examples showing how you can utilize language models (e.g., ChatGPT or Bard): argument analysis, evaluation of strengths and weaknesses, preparation for public speaking, text and information analysis, role simulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech&#39;s Rapid Growth: A Challenge for Humanity</title>
      <link>https://edu-transformer.github.io/abs/2310.0001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edu-transformer.github.io/abs/2310.0001/</guid>
      <description>Tech&amp;rsquo;s Rapid Growth: A Challenge for Humanity Source: Nobel Prize YouTube Channel, Abstract: GTP-4, Publication: 26 Paź 2023Tristan Harris discusses the rapid growth of technology, especially artificial intelligence (AI) and social media&amp;rsquo;s impact. Highlighting a challenge, he cites EO Wilson, a renowned sociobiologist, who said:
&amp;ldquo;The real problem of humanity is that we have Paleolithic emotions, medieval institutions, and god-like Technology.&amp;rdquo;
This quote underscores the gap between our basic emotions, old institutions, and powerful modern tech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unknown Explorer: Passion and Curiosity about the World</title>
      <link>https://edu-transformer.github.io/explorer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edu-transformer.github.io/explorer/</guid>
      <description>Unknown Explorer The world around us and our understanding of it are constantly evolving. Therefore, an open mind and curiosity are essential for learning and personal growth. Do you want to understand how our brain works and how it relates to the GPT model? Would you like to create your own language model? How does mathematics, biology, and the English language relate to all this? We encourage you to conduct your own research and explore the topics that intrigue you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update Integrator: Integrate current reality with education</title>
      <link>https://edu-transformer.github.io/integrator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edu-transformer.github.io/integrator/</guid>
      <description>Update Integrator We live in an era of constant information flow, which can sometimes be overwhelming. At the same time, our curriculum might occasionally feel disconnected from the rapidly changing world around us. Ever wondered why some news grabs your attention more than others? We are guided by algorithms focused on clickability, not content value.
Instead of passively consuming news, let&amp;rsquo;s become &amp;lsquo;Update Integrators&amp;rsquo;. By doing this, we can bridge the gap between our current reality and educational content.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
